[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where was the 2000 comedy Big Mommas House, starring Martin Lawrence, filmed?", "correct_answer": "California, USA", "incorrect_answers": ["Paris, France", "Dusseldorf, Germany", "Sidney, Australia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The smallest species of shark in the world is the Dwarf Lanternfish.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the lawyer that De Niros character was stalking in the movie Cape Fear?", "correct_answer": "Nick Nolte", "incorrect_answers": ["Donald Sutherland", "Robert Mitchum", "Jeff Bridges"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What former president has addressed more than a million people on many occasions on Plaza de la Revoluci\u00f3n in Havana?", "correct_answer": "Fidel Castro", "incorrect_answers": ["Benito Mussolini", "Salvador Allende", "Francisco Franco"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the original mascot for the Cookie Crisp cereal?", "correct_answer": "a wizard", "incorrect_answers": ["a bear", "a masked man", "an animated cookie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why did Brian get a Saturday detention in the film The Breakfast Club?", "correct_answer": "He was going to kill himself", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "He had pot and marijuana", "He killed someone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Twilight Zone is a term used by the United States Air Force to describe the border between day and night on a planetary body.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Although the movie My Girl was set in the summer of 1972, it was released in this year.", "correct_answer": "1991", "incorrect_answers": ["1993", "1990", "1992"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Grand Strand is a long stretch of sandy beach situated near which of the following?", "correct_answer": "Myrtle Beach", "incorrect_answers": ["Hilton Head", "Follie Beach", "Charleston"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does Turkey belong only in Asia?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these Star Wars heroes was a former Imperial Officer?", "correct_answer": "Han Solo", "incorrect_answers": ["Greedo", "Chewbacca", "Yoda"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This device is pretty useful if you have to walk a mile in the dark.", "correct_answer": "Mobile LED Light", "incorrect_answers": ["Bluetooth Car Handset", "Mobile UV Money Detector", "Lithium Battery"]}]